pageonerankings.com.au 2019-03-06

# Privacy Policy | PageOneRankings Australia

## OutsourcingTo.uS Pty Ltd (PageOneRankings.com.au), are committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the Privacy Act 1998. This Privacy Policy describes our current policies and practices in relation to the handling and use of personal information.

  1. **What information do we collect and how do we use it?**
    1. As an online marketing service provider we are subject to legislative and regulatory requirements to obtain and hold detailed information which identifies your company and/or business. In addition, to providing you with an SEO advisory service we need to obtain certain information about your company. We provide any information that any other engaged advisor (such as: SEO directory owners, website owners) whom we deal with on your behalf need to implement your online marketing strategies.
    2. We also use your information to send to other website owners to enable us to manage your ongoing rankings and SEO requirements.
    3. We may occasionally notify you about new services and special offers, events or articles we think will be of interest to you. We may send you regular updates by email or by post on internet marketing advisory matters. If you would rather not receive this information or do not wish to receive it electronically, email or write to us.
    4. We may use your information internally to help us improve our services and help resolve any problems.
  2. **What if you don’t provide some information to us?**
    1. We can only fully implement your SEO marketing services if we have all relevant information. If the information you provide is inaccurate or incomplete, our advice may not be suitable for your needs and circumstances.
  3. **How do we hold and protect your information?**
    1. We strive to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of the personal information we hold and to protect its privacy and security. We keep personal information only for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purpose for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or document retention requirements.
    2. We have access to the information collected from you using secure external online server facility powered by our software partners as listed on our website. We will strive to maintain the privacy of this data for our part, but we encourage you to ensure you practice the highest level of online security at all times.
    3. We ensure that your information is safe by limiting access to your company data to your adviser and his/her associate as requested. An External Auditor may request access to any of our files for the purpose of compliance audit only and you will be advised in this instance.
  4. **Will we disclose the information we collect to anyone?**
    1. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others rather we use the information you provide such as press releases, SEO copy and content to deliver your requirements and thereby increase your rankings.
    2. We may need to provide your information to contractors who supply services to us, e.g. to handle SEO submissions on our behalf or to other companies in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganisation, dissolution or similar event. However, we will do our best to ensure that they protect your information in the same way that we do. As an example: we may disclose your company website information to external contractors for the following purposes:
      1. storing information;
      2. creating inbound links to your website
      3. on-page optimization methods to your webmaster or chosen web design firm
    3. We may provide your information to others if we are required to do so by law or under some unusual other circumstances which the Privacy Act permits.
  5. **How can you check, update or change the information we are holding?**
    1. Upon receipt of your written request and enough information to allow us to identify the information, we will disclose to you the company information we hold about you. We will also correct, amend or delete any personal information that we agree is inaccurate. All this information is collated and stored securely in your [Basecamp](http://basecamphq.com/) account which you and our team managers have access to.
  6. **Internet Sites**
    1. If you have confirmed an SEO campaign with us and decide, at any time, that you do not wish to receive any further information from us, you can either send an email to the e-mail address noted below requesting to be removed from our online registration database or simply tick “unsubscribe” on your last piece of electronic mail from OUTSOURCINGTOUS (PAGEONERANKINGS) . Please allow two weeks for your request to be actioned if it’s requested to be done manually.
    2. You may amend or update your registration details by sending an email to the email address noted below providing your amended details. Please allow one week for your request to be actioned. Our website/s may use cookies, which would allow us to identify your users browsers while they are using your site. Cookies do not identify you; they simply allow us to track usage patterns so that we can measure the level of interest in various areas of your site. All browsers allow you to be notified when you receive a cookie and elect to either accept it or not. Your Internet service provider should be able to assist you to set your preferences.
  7. **Your consent**
    1. By asking us to assist with your SEO, Link Building and other optimization services, you consent to the collection and use of the information you have provided to us for the purposes described above.

## About our SEO services

  * You should only engage SEO firms with credibility and critically, proof. We offer both.
  * Not on the 1st page of the search engines? You are losing 80% of your potential searchers.
  * Work with a team that engages the [top media research company](http://www.nielsenmedia.com/nc/portal/site/Public/) to analyse our own sites.
  * You need 1st page and position 1 results. We'll help you get there.
  * We use the same team and methods as we do on our own large network of sites.
  * We specialize in SEO, link building and local search marketing.
  * We have over 1000 online marketing campaigns deployed over the last 10 years.
  * We have a solid reputation with Testimonials and an excellent international portfolio.
  * We additionally offer international outsourcing services via [OutsourcingTo.uS](http://outsourcingto.us/).
  * Our rates are very affordable as we have an offshore team in Manila.
